Guide to the Records of the Public History Program RG.20.9
New York University Archives
- Series VI: Media
  - 1978-1988
    - Anita Gulkin interview, Greenwich House, 1/14/1987, Copy, cuid3345 (Box 7, Object 35)
      It can be assumed that this interview was conducted for the 1987 Public History Workshop, which focused on the history of the Greenwich House settlement. Anita Gulkin was the Director of Greenwich House at the time of this interview.
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, 'Greenwich House Catechism' presentation, 1986-1987; cuid3346 (Box 7, Object 36)
      It can be assumed that this cassette is related to the 1987 Public History Workshop, which focused on the history of the Greenwich House settlement organization.
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, "Greenwich Village Catechism" presentation (Copy), 1986-1987; cuid3347 (Box 7, Object 37)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, slides, cuid3348 (Box 7, Object 38)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, slides, cuid3349 (Box 7, Object 39)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, slides, cuid3350 (Box 7, Object 40)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, slides, cuid3351 (Box 7, Object 41)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, slides, cuid3352 (Box 7, Object 42)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, slides, cuid3353 (Box 7, Object 43)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, slides, cuid3354 (Box 7, Object 44)
    - Alice Kaslow Interview by Laura O'Loughlin, 12/5/1987, cuid3355 (Box 7, Object 45)
      pro II chrome BASF90 Audio Cassette
    - "Work and the Waterways: An Oral History of the Midwestern Workers," Parts 1 and 2, 1987; cuid3356 (Box 7, Object 46)
      Contained on this audio cassette is a documentary program entitled: 'Work and the Waterways: An Oral History of the Midwestern Workers.' It is copyrighted 1987, by Loyola University of Chicago's Public History program. Parts 1 and 2 are located on Sides A and B respectively.
      Unspecific audio cassette
    - 'McGraw', Aug. 20, 1987, cuid3357 (Box 7, Object 47)
      BASF LH-EI 90 Audio Cassette
    - "Generations," 1988, cuid3358 (Box 7, Object 48)
    - Washington Square Workshop, 1988, Part 1, cuid413 (Box 7, Cassette 49, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid413, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 29)
      Format: VHS, Duration: 103 min.
    - Washington Square Workshop, 1988, Part 2, cuid414 (Box 7, Cassette 50, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid414)
      Format: VHS, Duration: [unknown]
    - Chelsea Workshop, 1982-83, slides (35mm slides), 1982-1983; cuid3361 (Box 7, Object 53)
    - Washington Square Workshop, 1988, slides (35mm slides), cuid3362 (Box 7, Object 54)
    - Washington Square Workshop, 1988, slides (35mm slides), cuid3363 (Box 7, Object 55)
    - Washington Square Workshop, 1988, slides (35mm slides), cuid3364 (Box 7, Object 56)
    - 'Image as Artifact,' John E. O'Connor, American Historical Association, 1987, cuid3365 (Box 15, Object 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227580-3
  - 1989-1993
    - "Camp Midvale: An Oral History," 1988, cuid3366 (Box 8, Cassette 1)
      Dolby B Audio Cassette
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227307-1
    - Anna Schulman Interview, 4/10/1988, cuid3367 (Box 8, Cassette 2)
    - Louis and Gloria DeSantis interview, by Laura O'Loughlin and Sean Holmes, 4/19/1988, cuid3368 (Box 8, Cassette 3)
      Maxell UR90 Audio Cassette
    - Louis and Gloria DeSantis interview, by Laura O'Loughlin and Sean Holmes, 4/19/1988, Copy, cuid3369 (Box 8, Cassette 4)
    - Anne Pascarelli and Irene Miller interview, 4/28/1988, cuid3370 (Box 8, Cassette 5)
      TDK SA-C90 Audio Cassette
      Side A's contents is somewhat uncertain -- perhaps a play? There is music on Side B of this cassette.
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, 'Violets on the Picket Line,' Peter Miller documentary, Copy 1, cuid3371 (Box 8, Cassette 6)
      U-matic: 3/4 in. analog
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, 'Violets on the Picket Line,' Peter Miller documentary, Copy 2, cuid3372 (Box 8, Cassette 7)
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, Tape 1 (dub), Copy 1, cuid415 (Box 8, Cassette 8, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid415, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 30)
      Format: VHS, Duration: 101 min.; Displays burnt-in timecode.
      Housing Annotations
      Label reads: May, 1989 - Public History Seminar #1 "Uneasy Alliance" - NYU
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, Tape 2 (dub), Copy 1, cuid417 (Box 8, Cassette 10, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid417, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 31)
      Fomrat: VHS, Duration: 123 min.
      Label reads: May, 1989 - Public History Seminar Tape #2 (Dub) "Uneasy Alliance" - NYU and Its Communities
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, Tape 3 (dub), Copy 1, cuid418 (Box 8, Cassette 11, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid418, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 32)
      Format: VHS, Duration: 6 min.
      Housing Annotations:
      Label reads: May, 1989 - Public History Seminar Tape #3 (Dub) "Uneasy Alliance" - NYU and Its Communities 20 Minutes final comments
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, Susan DeMark Presentation, cuid3373 (Box 8, Cassette 13)
    - 'Disobeying Orders': GI Resistance to the Vietnam War, 1989, cuid3374 (Box 8, Cassette 14)
    - Alice Kaslow interview, 12/4/1989, cuid3375 (Box 8, Cassette 15)
      Interviewer
      The Public History student who is interviewing Alice Kaslow on this tape is Laura O'Loughlin.
    - Slides, Working Women, early-mid 20th century, 1980s transfer, cuid3376 (Box 8, Object 16)
    - Slides, Working Women, early-mid 20th century, 1980s transfer, cuid3377 (Box 8, Object 17)
    - Slides, Working Women, early-mid 20th century, 1980s transfer, cuid3378 (Box 8, Object 18)
    - Slides, Working Women, early-mid 20th century, 1980s transfer, cuid3379 (Box 8, Object 19)
    - Slides, Female Students at NYU, early 20th century, 1980s transfer, cuid3380 (Box 8, Object 20)
    - Slides, Catherine Jones Project, 'Death & Disease', 1980s undated, cuid3381 (Box 8, Object 21)
    - "New Yorkers at Work: Oral Histories of Life, Labor, and Industry," Parts 3 and 4, cuid3382 (Box 8, Cassette 22)
      Additional information
      The program contained on this audio cassette is a product of the Documentary Radio Series and noted as "property of the program in Public History."
      Part 3 of the series is entitled, "Hard Times and Picket Lines: The 30s and the CIO"
      Part 4 of the series is entitled, "Solidarity Asunder: Labor After the War"
      The producer of this series is: Margaret Low
      Audio cassette
    - "New Yorkers at Work: Oral Histories of Life, Labor, and Industry," Parts 5 and 6, cuid3383 (Box 8, Cassette 23)
      Additional Information
      Part 5 of the series is entitled, "Climbing That Ladder: Jobs and Opportunity"
      Part 6 of the series is entitled, "Bargaining, Bail-out, Burn-out: Public Employees and the Service Crisis"
      The producers of this series are: Phaye Poliakoff and Debra Bernhardt
    - "New Yorkers at Work: Oral Histories of Life, Labor, and Industry," Parts 7 and 8, cuid3384 (Box 8, Cassette 24)
      Part 7 of the series is entitled, "Sixty Words per minute: Clericals have their Say"
      Part 8 of the series is entitled, "Where Have all the Jobs Gone? The Eighties"
      The producers of this series are: Lori Ciffi and Debra Bernhardt
    - "New Yorkers at Work: Oral Histories of Life, Labor, and Industry," copy of Parts 7 and 8, cuid3385 (Box 8, Cassette 25)
    - Meeting with Friends of Washington Square Park, Tape 1, 1980s undated, cuid3386 (Box 8, Cassette 26)
      Technical problems
      The audio on this cassette is very poor, and the first ten minutes are not audible at all.
    - Meeting with Friends of Washington Square Park, Tape 2, 1980s undated, cuid3387 (Box 8, Cassette 27)
      Only 10 minutes of this tape are audible.
    - Margaret Bourke White's NYC Photography, slides, cuid3388 (Box 8, Object 28)
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1990, Tape 1 (Copy 1), cuid420 (Box 8, Cassette 29, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid420, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 33)
      Format: VHS, Duration: 29 min.
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1990, Tape 1 (Copy 2), cuid3389 (Box 8, Object 30)
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1990, Tape 2, cuid421 (Box 8, Cassette 31, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid421, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 34)
      Format: VHS, Duration: 102 min.
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1990, User's Tape/Dub, cuid3390 (Box 8, Object 32)
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1990, slides, cuid3391 (Box 8, Object 33)
      Attached object
      In the same container as these slides is an empty film strip, with no visible material stored on it.
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1990, slides, cuid3392 (Box 8, Object 34)
    - Kai-Mon Chin interview, 1990, by Stacey Bell, cuid3393 (Box 8, Object 35)
      This oral history interview was likely conducted for use in the Chinatown Public History Workshop of 1990.
    - Dr. Paul Chu interview, 3/30/1990, original, cuid3394 (Box 8, Object 36)
      Maxell UDX-II 90, Audio Cassette
      There is reason to assume that this oral history interview is related to the 1990 Public History Workshop, which focused on the relations between Chinese and Italian immigrants on the Lower East Side.
    - Dr. Paul Chu interview, 3/30/1990, copy, cuid3395 (Box 8, Object 37)
    - Norman Chin interview, 5/1990, by Stacey Bell, cuid3396 (Box 8, Object 38)
      Sony HF UX90 Audio Cassette
      The oral history interview on this cassette is likely related to the 1990 Public History Workshop, which focused on relations between Italian and Chinese immigrants on the Lower East Side.
    - BBC World Service: 'Trotsky,' 8/20/1990, by Andy Lanset, cuid3397 (Box 8, Object 39)
      The business card of Andy Lanset, the director of this documentary, is attached to this cassette.
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Tape 1 of 3, cuid422 (Box 8, Cassette 40, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid422, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 35)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 62 min.
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Tape 2 of 3, cuid423 (Box 8, Cassette 41, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid423, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 36)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 60 min.
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Tape 3 of 3, cuid424 (Box 8, Cassette 42, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid424, Box Shared Access 16, Disk 37)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Part 1, cuid3398 (Box 8, Object 43)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Part 2, cuid3399 (Box 8, Object 44)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Tape #1 of 3, cuid3400 (Box 8, Object 45)
      Hi-8 Video Cassette, P6-60HMPX
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Tape #2 of 3, cuid3401 (Box 8, Object 46)
      Sony Hi-8 P6-60HMPX, Video Cassette
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Tape #3 of 3, cuid3402 (Box 8, Object 47)
      Sony Hi-8 P6-30HMPX, Video Cassette
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Rehearsal #1, cuid3403 (Box 8, Object 48)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Rehearsal #2, cuid3404 (Box 8, Object 49)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1991, Rehearsal #3, cuid3405 (Box 8, Object 50)
    - Von Steuben House Field Trip, 1991, Tape 1, cuid3406 (Box 8, Object 51)
    - Von Steuben House Field Trip, 1991, Tape 2, cuid3407 (Box 8, Object 52)
      Note attached that states: 'Steuben/Demarast/Campbell-Christie; ambient sound at end'
      Hi-8 Metal-P Video Cassette, P6-60HMPX
    - 'Scottsboro: A Civil Rights Milestone,' NPR Horizons, 3/1991, cuid3408 (Box 8, Object 53)
      The tape contain a documentary produced by NPR Horizons, and created by Andy Lanset, released in March 1991. The formal title of the documentary is: 'Scottsboro: A Civil Rights Milestone'
    - Sanger pictures, 5/13/1991, cuid3409 (Box 8, Object 54)
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, "Violets on the Picket Line," by Peter Miller, cuid3410 (Box 8, Object 55)
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, slides (35mm slides), cuid3411 (Box 8, Object 56)
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, slides (35mm slides), cuid3412 (Box 8, Object 57)
    - NYU Workshop, 1989, slides (35mm slides), cuid3413 (Box 8, Object 58)
    - Richard Berkley, Unused slides for Public History project, 1989, cuid3414 (Box 8, Object 59)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 1, cuid3415 (Box 9, Object 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227308-9
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 2, cuid3416 (Box 9, Object 2)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 3, cuid3417 (Box 9, Object 3)
      Hi-8 Metal-P Video Cassette, Sony
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 1 (dub), cuid3418 (Box 9, Object 4)
      Maxell T60 M10 VHS Cassette
      Individuals represented
      The presentations/speeches of the following individuals are included on this cassette: V. Shaffer, P. Mattingly, Tim Allison, Renee Newman.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 2 (dub), cuid3419 (Box 9, Object 5)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 3 (dub), cuid3420 (Box 9, Object 6)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 1 of 3, cuid3421 (Box 9, Object 7)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 2 of 3, cuid3422 (Box 9, Object 8)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 3 of 3, cuid3423 (Box 9, Object 9)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, slides, cuid3424 (Box 9, Object 10)
    - Tenement Museum Trip, 9/30/1992, cuid3425 (Box 9, Object 11)
    - Ernest & Elaine Cohn interview, 1992, by Matthew Moshen, cuid3426 (Box 9, Object 12)
      HF-60 Audio Cassette
    - Sally Stern Interview, 1992, by Sharon Laist, Copy 1, cuid3427 (Box 9, Object 13)
    - Sally Stern Interview, 1992, by Sharon Laist, Copy 2, cuid3428 (Box 9, Object 14)
    - Sushan Chin Interview, 1992, by Rebecca Epstein, Copy 1, cuid3429 (Box 9, Object 15)
    - Sushan Chin Interview, 1992, by Rebecca Epstein, Copy 2, cuid3430 (Box 9, Object 16)
    - Oral History Project, 1992, 60s Student Activism, Interview with David Hicks, cuid3431 (Box 9, Object 17)
    - Oral History Project, 1992, 60s Student Activism, Interview with Joel Shapiro, cuid3432 (Box 9, Object 18)
    - Oral History Project, 1992, 60s Student Activism, Interview with Marisol Maldenado, cuid3433 (Box 9, Object 19)
      Audio Cassette
    - Oral History Project, 1992, 60s Student Activism, Interview with John Mason, Part 1 of 2, cuid3434 (Box 9, Object 20)
    - Oral History Project, 1992, 60s Student Activism, Interview with John Mason, Part 1 of 2, cuid3435 (Box 9, Object 21)
    - Oral History Project, 1992, 60s Student Activism, Interview with Emma Jordan, cuid3436 (Box 9, Object 22)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, May Witte/Herbert King (recorded c. 1978), cuid3437 (Box 9, Cassette 23, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3437)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 52 min.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Herbert King (recorded c. 1978), cuid3438 (Box 9, Cassette 24, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3438)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 44 min.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Lawrence Frost/Howard Merlin (recorded c. 1978), cuid3439 (Box 9, Cassette 25, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3439)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 54 min.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Martin & Mireille Langeman (recorded c. 1978), cuid3440 (Box 9, Cassette 26, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3440)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 94 min.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Mary Kay & John Gallagher (recorded c. 1978), cuid3441 (Box 9, Cassette 27, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3341)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 87 min.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Hein Juergensen (recorded c. 1978), cuid3442 (Box 9, Cassette 28, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3442)
      Foramt: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 34 min.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Louis Wolff (recorded c. 1978), cuid3443 (Box 9, Cassette 29, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3343)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, James E. Davis (recorded c. 1991), cuid3444 (Box 9, Cassette 30, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3444)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, James E. Davis (recorded c. 1991), cuid3445 (Box 9, Cassette 31, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3445)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 91 min.
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Olga Tong (recorded c. 1991), cuid3446 (Box 9, Cassette 32, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3446)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Herbert E. King (recorded c. 1991), cuid3447 (Box 9, Cassette 33A, 33B, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid3447A, cuid3447B)
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 94 min. [A] and 29 minutes [B]
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Larry Frost, cuid3448 (Box 9, Object 34)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, May Witte/Herbert E. King, cuid3449 (Box 9, Object 35)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Group Session, Conyer & Greene, cuid3450 (Box 9, Object 36)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Herbert E. King, cuid3451 (Box 9, Object 37)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Louis Wolff, cuid3452 (Box 9, Object 38)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Howard Merlin, cuid3453 (Box 9, Object 39)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Oral History Interview, Hein Juergensen, cuid3454 (Box 9, Object 40)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Charmaine's project, cuid3455 (Box 9, Object 41)
      Two (2) floppy disks
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 1 of 3, cuid3456 (Box 9, Object 42)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 2 of 3, cuid3457 (Box 9, Object 43)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1992, Tape 3 of 3, cuid3458 (Box 9, Object 44)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Tape 1, cuid3459 (Box 9, Object 45)
    - 'Henry Street Settlement,' documentary, for Henry Street Workshop, 1993, cuid3460 (Box 9, Object 46)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Tape 1, cuid3461 (Box 9, Object 47)
      Attached label notes that Candance Sorensen, Jane McNamara, Jacob Patent, Don Doherty are featured on this cassette.
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Tape 2, cuid3462 (Box 9, Object 48)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Tape 3, Copy 1, cuid3463 (Box 9, Object 49)
      The workshop presentations included on this tape represent the work of: Greg Raynor, Sean Reilly, Rachel Bernstein, and a panel discussion
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Tape 3, Copy 2, cuid3464 (Box 9, Object 50)
      Hi-8 video cassette
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Rehearsal, Part 1, cuid3465 (Box 9, Object 51)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Rehearsal, Part 2, cuid3466 (Box 9, Object 52)
    - 'World that Moses Built,' American Experience, 1989, cuid3467 (Box 16, Object 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227581-1
    - 'The Road to Mississippi: Reclaiming Our History,' Through Out Eyes Video & History Project, 1990, cuid3468 (Box 16, Object 2)
    - Sam Dolgoff (nterviewed by Oral History class), 10/4/1990, cuid3469 (Box 16, Object 3, Box Shared Access 13, Item 56)
      Maxell XL HIFI 120 VHS Cassette Tape
    - '2nd Washington Square Film Sessions, Greg & Janet,' 2/1/1991, cuid3470 (Box 16, Object 4)
      Hi-8 Video Cassette, SONY P6-60HMP Metal-P
    - 'Casting the First Stone,' Julie Gustafson, 1991, cuid3471 (Box 16, Object 5)
    - 'May Day in Union Square,' Joan Cowen Brancaccio, Spring 1991 (WordPerfect 5.1, document name: draft3), cuid3472 (Box 16, Object 6)
      3.5" Diskette
    - 'The Big Apple,' a short video history of the City of New York, narrated by Bill Beutel, and produced by the Museum of the City of New York, 1992, cuid3473 (Box 16, Object 7)
    - 'Passin' It On: The Story of a Black Panther's Search for Justice,' First Run Features, 1993, cuid3474 (Box 16, Object 8)
    - 'East Side Story: Visions of Youth on Henry Street,' Greg Raynor, 1993, cuid3475 (Box 16, Object 9)
      Two (2) VHS Cassette Tapes
  - 1994-1999
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Dub Tape 1, Copy 1, cuid3476 (Box 10, Object 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227309-7
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, Dub Tape 1, Copy 2, cuid3477 (Box 10, Object 2)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, slides, 'From Neighbors to Clients?', cuid3478 (Box 10, Object 3)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, slides, 'From Neighbors to Clients?', cuid3479 (Box 10, Object 4)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, slides, 'The Drama of Henry Street', cuid3480 (Box 10, Object 5)
    - "Everyone Knows It's Slinky," documentary, 1994, cuid3481 (Box 10, Object 6)
    - Steven Brier presentation, 'What Is Public History?,' 3/28/1995, Copy 1, cuid425 (Box 10, Cassette 7, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid425)
      Format: Hi8mm, Duration: 63 min.
      An attached note states that this cassette is dated 3/28/1994, though the label on the actual tape claims 3/28/1995. The processing of this item will align with the date on the cassette itself (1995), though it should be noted that this discrepancy exists.
    - Steven Brier presentation, 'What is Public History?,' 3/28/1995, Copy 2, cuid3482 (Box 10, Object 8)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Rehearsal, Tape 1, 1996; cuid3483 (Box 10, Object 9)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Rehearsal, Tape 2, cuid3484 (Box 10, Object 10)
      On this cassette is a skit arranged for this workshop, entitled: Easter with Matzos and Bintel Brief, The Bowery.
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Introductory presentations, 4/30/95, cuid426 (Box 10, Cassette 11, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid426)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Introductory Presentations, cuid3485 (Box 10, Object 12)
    - 'An Immigrant Mother' documentary, Lower East Side Workshop, 1995, cuid427 (Box 10, Cassette 13, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid427)
      This cassette was likely used for the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on life in the Lower East Side neighborhood.
      Format: Hi8mm, Duration: 11 min.
    - 'Easter with Matzohs: The Bowery' documentary, Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Copy 1, cuid428 (Box 10, Cassette 14, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid428)
      It can be hypothesized that this item was used for the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on life in the Lower East Side.
      Format: Hi8mm, Duration: 46 min.
    - 'Easter with Matzohs: The Bowery' documentary, Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Copy 2, cuid3486 (Box 10, Object 15)
      It can be hypothesized that this cassette was used in conjunction with the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on immigrant life in the Lower East Side neighborhood.
    - Leon Birns Interview #1, by Ellen Noonan and John Spencer, 10/16/95, 1995; cuid3487 (Box 10, Object 16)
      Sony, Hi-8 Video Cassette, P6-60HMPX
      It can be assumed that this oral history interview was used in conjunction with the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on immigrant life in the Lower East Side neighborhood.
    - Leon Birns interview #2, 10/16/1995, cuid3488 (Box 10, Object 17)
      Attached note to cassette
      There was a note attached to the cassette that reads: 'this tape already dumped; see 3/4 to right side of machine'.
    - Leon Birns interview #2, 10/24/1995, by C. Turek and M. Menechella, cuid3489 (Box 10, Object 18)
    - Leon Birns Interview, Master Edit, 10/30/1995, cuid3490 (Box 10, Object 19)
      Tape characteristics
      This tape contains an edited interview. It does not rewind easily and delivers a loud, high-pitched sound.
    - Lower East Side location shots and Leon Birns Interview, 10/24/1995, cuid3491 (Box 10, Object 20)
      Related Event/Material